Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - Commerce and SBA Appeal Materials (Box-folder 95: 9)
  - PAD Review Book (Box-folder 95: 10)
  - 1984 DOT Appeals (Box-folder 96: 1)
  - Brief Summary of Director’s Decisions Being Passed Back to Departments or Agencies (Box-folder 96: 2)
  - Department of Commerce-1983 Budget Passback (Box-folder 96: 3)
  - 1983 Spring Planning Review-Office of Federal Procurement Policy (Box-folder 96: 4)
  - DOC Appeal Material – December 2, 1981 (Box-folder 96: 5)
  - DOT Appeal 1983 Budget (Box-folder 96: 6)
  - Commerce (Box-folder 96: 7-8)
  - FSLIC Cash Flow (Box-folder 96: 9)
  - Federal National Mortgage Association (FNMA) (Box-folder 96: 10)
  - Thrifts Conference Action (Box-folder 96: 11)
  - ICCs/Scoring (Box-folder 96: 12)
  - Cash Flows (Box-folder 96: 13)
  - Due-on-sale decision: FYI (Box-folder 96: 14)
  - House Offer to the Senate in the Matter of the Disagreement between the Two Houses on H.R. 6267 (Box-folder 97: 1)
  - GNMA Mortgage-Backed Securities Program Status Report (Box-folder 97: 2)
  - Reagan Administration Housing Policies (Box-folder 97: 3)
  - FHLBB/FSLIC (Box-folder 97: 4)
  - Implementation of the Net Worth Certificate Program (Box-folder 97: 5)
  - Mortgage Market (Box-folder 97: 6)
  - Fat Children of Housing Credit (Box-folder 97: 7)
  - First draft report on deposit interest rate regulation (Box-folder 97: 8)
  - Freddie Mac (Box-folder 97: 9)
  - Thrift Legislation (Box-folder 97: 10)
  - Appeals Process (Box-folder 97: 11)
  - Constraining Federal Taxing and Spending – October 21-23, 1981 (Box-folder 97: 12-14)
  - 1984 Fall Director’s Review – The Economic Outlook (Box-folder 97: 15)
  - 1984 Budget Documents (Box-folder 97: 16)
  - Thrift Outlook Conference – December 3, 1982 (Box-folder 97: 17)
  - The President’s FY 1984 Budget Freeze and Reform Plan (Box-folder 97: 18)
  - TIMS (Box-folder 98: 1-2)
  - Part 1-Budget Totals-President’s Budget Freeze and Reform Plan (Box-folder 98: 3)
  - Statement by Donald T. Regan (Box-folder 98: 4)
  - FFB – OFF -Budget Issue (Box-folder 98: 5)
  - Spring Review – 82 (Box-folder 98: 6)
  - Treasury – 1984 Budget (Box-folder 98: 7)
  - Highways 84 Planning (Box-folder 98: 8)
  - DOJ (Box-folder 98: 9)
  - Justice (Box-folder 98: 10)
  - 1984 Spring Planning Review-Justice, Treasury and General Management (Box-folder 98: 11)
  - Summary of 1984 Director’s Review Book (Box-folder 98: 12)
  - Advances to the Government of the District of Columbia (Box-folder 98: 13)
  - Property Review Board Sales Estimates for Fiscal Years 1983 and 1984 (Box-folder 98: 14)
  - Customs Service Changes and Customs/INS Border Inspection (Box-folder 98: 15)
  - Effect of Pay and Retirement Contribution Increase on Take-Home-Pay (Box-folder 98: 16)
  - Federal Health Benefit Program (Box-folder 98: 17)
  - Forecasts (Box-folder 98: 18)
  - 1984 Budget (Box-folder 99: 1-2)
  - Letter to John Buchanan from Julia Gould – Budget Examiner (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - Civil Service Retirement Proposals (Box-folder 99: 4)
  - President’s Entitlement 1 Decisions (Box-folder 99: 5-6)
  - President’s Entitlement Meeting – December 15, 1982 (Box-folder 99: 7)
  - Personnel Policies (Box-folder 99: 8)
  - Retirement – 1984 (Box-folder 99: 9)
  - New OPM Information on Dynamic Normal Cost of CRS (Box-folder 99: 10)
  - “Typical” Private Sector Retirement Plan (Box-folder 99: 11)
  - Further Considerations on Overgrading (Box-folder 99: 12)
  - Private Sector/Federal Salary Comparisons (Box-folder 99: 13)
  - February 9 Meeting of President’s Pay Agent and Federal Employees Pay Council (FEPC) (Box-folder 99: 14)
  - Data on grades, promotions, and turnover (Box-folder 99: 15)
  - Federal Employee Job Overgrading (Box-folder 99: 16)
  - Legislative/Reconciliation related notes (Box-folder 99: 17)
  - 1985 Spring Planning Review – Pension Demograph (Box-folder 100: 1)
  - Entitlements (Box-folder 100: 2)
  - Personnel Policy Task Force Meeting – August 6, 1982 (Box-folder 100: 3)
  - Personnel (Retirement) (Box-folder 100: 4)
  - Civil Service Clippings – Washington Post (Box-folder 100: 5)
  - Civil Service Retirement System (Box-folder 100: 6)
  - Overview of OPM Appeal (Box-folder 100: 7)
  - Federal Personnel Policy Division, OMB Overview (Box-folder 100: 8)
  - Central Personnel Data File-Report: Change in Average Grade Report (Box-folder 100: 9)
  - OID (Box-folder 100: 10)
  - Final Presidential Entitlements Summary (Box-folder 100: 11)
  - HUD Authorization (Box-folder 100: 12)
  - Omnibus Reconciliation Act of 1981-attached copy (Box-folder 100: 13)
  - Markup Materials for the Second Budget Resolution Fiscal Year 1982 – October 7, 1981 (Box-folder 101: 1-2)
  - Gramm-Latta Amendment – Overview and Summary (Box-folder 101: 3)
  - Status of Administration-Sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 1st Session (Box-folder 101: 4)
  - OMB Staff Comparisons of Provisions of Dingell and Broyhill – Energy and Commerce (Box-folder 101: 5)
  - Explanation of the Changes Provided for in the Gramm-Latta Amendment (Box-folder 101: 6-7)
  - Rail Service Improvement Act of 1981 (Box-folder 101: 8)
  - House Budget Committee Meeting on November 5 (Box-folder 101: 9)
  - Calendar of Events – Testimony and other Legislative Affairs (Box-folder 101: 10)
  - Understanding the Budget, Authorization, Appropriations and Apportionment Process During 1981 (Box-folder 101: 11)
  - Banking (Box-folder 101: 12)
  - Transportation – Auth. (Box-folder 101: 13)
  - Gram-Latta II (Box-folder 101: 14)
  - Merchant Marine (Box-folder 102: 1)
  - CDF (Box-folder 102: 2)
  - Revised Draft of the House Energy Committee Republican Alternative Dated 6-9-81 (Box-folder 102: 3)
  - Title XI—House Committee on Public Works and Transportation (Box-folder 102: 4)
  - Reconciliation recommendations proposed by the Committee on Public Works and Transportation (Box-folder 102: 5)
  - Public Works and Transportation (Box-folder 102: 6)
  - Changes in law to achieve cost savings (Box-folder 102: 7)
  - SBA (Box-folder 102: 8)
  - Title III—Housing, Community Development, Banking, and Related Programs (Box-folder 102: 9)
  - Introduction to Subtitle B (Box-folder 102: 10)
  - Administration HUD Bill (Box-folder 102: 11)
  - Consolidation of Community Development Block Grants and Urban Development Action Grants (Box-folder 102: 12)
  - HUD Reaction to “Working Draft” of Gramm-Latta II (Box-folder 102: 13)
  - Post Office etc. (Box-folder 102: 14)
  - Conrail (Box-folder 102: 15)
  - Legislative Strategy (Box-folder 102: 16)
  - Reconciliation (Box-folder 102: 17-18)
  - Reconciliation (Box-folder 103: 1)
  - HUD Authorization Bill (Box-folder 103: 2)
  - Hearings/Markups (Box-folder 103: 3)
  - Bill Status (Box-folder 103: 4)
  - Reconciliation-Note file (Box-folder 103: 5)
  - DAS Follow-up Instructions for Attached Letter from Tom Loeffler (Box-folder 103: 6)
  - Small Business Committee Reconciliation Mark-up (Box-folder 103: 7)
  - Draft of House Banking Committee Minority Views (Box-folder 103: 8)
  - Two copies of a restructured Housing and Community Development Amendments for 1981 (Box-folder 103: 9)
  - A Bill-Title I – Community and Economic Development Authorizations (Box-folder 103: 10)
  - Civilian Pay Cap (Box-folder 103: 11)
  - Tables of 1982 outlays (Box-folder 103: 12)
  - Advance to Farrell Lines (Box-folder 103: 13)
  - Reconciliation Notes (Box-folder 103: 14)
  - Northeast Problem (Box-folder 103: 15)
  - Fact Sheet on Social Security Minimum Benefit (Box-folder 103: 16)
  - Report from Candy Bryant – July 27, 1981 (Box-folder 103: 17)
  - TCH Exhibit 1 Materials—status reports on working assumptions (Box-folder 103: 18)
  - Status of Reconciliation Proposals (Box-folder 103: 19)
  - Multilateral Development Banks (Box-folder 103: 20)
  - Reconciliation tables (Box-folder 104: 1)
  - Sale of Silver from the National Defense Stockpile (Box-folder 104: 2)
  - Planning Assistance (Box-folder 104: 3)
  - Cumulative Effects of Some of the Administration’s Tax and Transfer Proposals (Box-folder 104: 4)
  - Federal Employment (Box-folder 104: 5)
  - The postal rate (Box-folder 104: 6)
  - Budget Committee/Legislative Affairs (Box-folder 104: 7)
  - JES2 Job Log (Box-folder 104: 8)
  - RIF System (Box-folder 104: 9)
  - Average Grade by Occupation tables (Box-folder 104: 10)
  - A negative allowance for grade reduction (Box-folder 104: 11)
  - OMB/OPM (Box-folder 104: 12)
  - Federal Employees Pay Council—Next Steps Before Scheduled July 20th Meeting (Box-folder 104: 13)
  - Statistics on Displacement and Bumping (Box-folder 104: 14)
  - Framework for Developing a Comprehensive Personnel Policy Package (Box-folder 104: 15)
  - Options for October 1982 Executive Pay Increases (Box-folder 104: 16)
  - FY 1983 budget resolution assumptions (Box-folder 104: 17)
  - Federal Personnel Policy Division (Box-folder 104: 18)
  - Management Initiatives (Box-folder 105: 1)
  - Personnel Management Spring Review Session (Box-folder 105: 2)
  - Issue Paper: Federal Employment Reduction and Other Possible Personnel Initiatives (Box-folder 105: 3)
  - AEC Occupational Staffing (Box-folder 105: 4)
  - CSRS-Employer Contributions (Box-folder 105: 5)
  - Retirement Task Force (Box-folder 105: 6)
  - CSR Unfunded Liability—Senator Stevens’ Comments (Box-folder 105: 7)
  - Meeting Between the Federal Employees Pay Council and the President’s Pay Agent (Box-folder 105: 8)
  - Social Security (Box-folder 105: 9)
  - Non-Defense Defense Threats (Box-folder 105: 10)
  - Personnel Task Force for Don Devine (Box-folder 105: 11)
  - Draft Pay Agent Report to the President (Box-folder 105: 12)
  - Weekly Activities Report – August 12, 1982 (Box-folder 105: 13)
  - Possible Areas for Inclusion in a Comprehensive Personnel Reform Package (Box-folder 105: 14)
  - Debate (Box-folder 105: 15)
  - Immigration (Box-folder 105: 16-20)
  - Immigration (Box-folder 106: 1)
  - T-1 Breakfast with Shultz/Immigration Legislation (Box-folder 106: 2)
  - Amendment to H.R. 6514 Offered by Mr. Lungren (Box-folder 106: 3)
  - Amendment to H.R. 6514, as reported by the Judiciary Committee offered by Mr. Miller of California (Box-folder 106: 4)
  - Reindustrialization (Box-folder 106: 5)
  - Proposed Agendas for Budget Briefings with the White House Intergovernmental Affairs Staff (Box-folder 106: 6)
  - Dinner Meeting with Housing Academics (Box-folder 106: 7)
  - Public Speaking Coordination (Box-folder 106: 8)
  - Republican National Committee (Box-folder 106: 9)
  - Highway construction (Box-folder 106: 10)
  - Administering Immigration and Refugee Policies (Box-folder 106: 11)
  - The German Marshall Fund of the United States (Box-folder 106: 12)
  - Wharton Public Policy Fellows (Box-folder 106: 13)
  - OMB – Preparing President’s 1983 Budget (Box-folder 106: 14)
  - Annual Report on the activities of the Hoover Institution – 1981-1982 (Box-folder 106: 15)
  - TRAC Forum on Transportation Systems Financing (Box-folder 106: 16)
  - Washington Welcomes Wellesley (Box-folder 106: 17)
  - Copies of recent articles on program reinstatement (Box-folder 106: 18)
  - Economy problems/recovery notes (Box-folder 106: 19)
  - Major Features of Budget Reform Plan (Box-folder 106: 20)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act of 1982 (Box-folder 106: 21)
  - Staff Review of USTR’s Trade Strategy Proposals (Box-folder 106: 22)
  - Simpson/Mazzoli Immigration Legislation 1982 (Box-folder 106: 23-24)
  - Cabinet Council on Natural Resources and Environment – July 8 Meeting (Box-folder 106: 25)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade – December 9, 1981 (Box-folder 106: 26)
  - Northeast/Midwest Economic Advisory (Box-folder 106: 27)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs – September 10 meeting (Box-folder 106: 28)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (Box-folder 106: 29)
  - Cabinet Councils – Other (Box-folder 106: 30)
  - CCEA minutes (Box-folder 106: 31)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (CCCT) (Box-folder 107: 1-2)
  - Material for Don Moran’s task force on entitlements (Box-folder 107: 3)
  - Applicability of retirement program proposals (Box-folder 107: 4)
  - Model of the Civil Service Retirement System (Box-folder 107: 5)
  - Analysis of the effect of our pay and retirement proposals on take-home pay (Box-folder 107: 6)
  - Federal Retirement Task Force (Box-folder 107: 7)
  - Employer Share of Retirement (Box-folder 107: 8)
  - Speech Notes 83 Budget (Box-folder 107: 9)
  - Christmas Open House Invitation from the White House (Box-folder 107: 10)
  - Materials for Speech – NYC (Box-folder 107: 11)
  - External Comments (Box-folder 107: 12)
  - The National Tax Limitation Committee (Box-folder 107: 13)
  - The Heritage Foundation – Issue Bulletin/International Briefing (Box-folder 107: 14)
  - Brookings – Twilight of Deregulation (Box-folder 107: 15)
  - Capital Formation-Supply Side Analysis and Public Policy (Box-folder 107: 16)
  - Cato Institute (Box-folder 107: 17)
  - Tax Foundation (Box-folder 107: 18)
  - The Great Seal and the concept for a Great Seal gold coin (Box-folder 107: 19)
  - Manhattan Report on Economic Policy (Box-folder 107: 20)
  - White Paper on Taxing and Spending Reduction (Box-folder 107: 21)
  - LRD (Box-folder 107: 22)
  - Cabinet Councils – AA Memos and notes (Box-folder 107: 23)
  - Cabinet Council on Natural Resources and Environment (Box-folder 107: 24)
  - CCLP (Box-folder 107: 25)
  - Cabinet Council on Legal Policy (Box-folder 107: 26)
  - CCLA (Box-folder 108: 1)
  - Cabinet Council notes/minutes (Box-folder 108: 2-3)
  - Cabinet Council on Food and Agriculture (Box-folder 108: 4)
  - Cabinet Council on Human Resources (Box-folder 108: 5)
  - Cabinet Council on Management and Administration (Box-folder 108: 6)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (CCCT) (Box-folder 108: 7-11)
  - Cabinet Council on Commerce and Trade (CCCT) (Box-folder 109: 1-2)
  - Cabinet Councils general notes (Box-folder 109: 3)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (CCEA) (Box-folder 109: 4-9)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs (CCEA) (Box-folder 110: 1-2)
  - Office of Cabinet Administration Issues Schedule (Box-folder 110: 3)
  - Status of Administration-sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 2nd Session (Box-folder 110: 4)
  - Tracking Log – October 15, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 5)
  - Cabinet Council on Management and Administration – January 12, 1983 (Box-folder 110: 6)
  - AG/BRB (Box-folder 110: 7)
  - Mid-term Planning Reviews – Transportation (Box-folder 110: 8)
  - Mid-Term Planning Session: Federal Emergency Management Agency (Box-folder 110: 9)
  - Memo for the President: Thrift Industry Legislative Proposals (Box-folder 110: 10)
  - Coal Severance Taxes (Box-folder 110: 11)
  - Meese/Harper Project (Box-folder 110: 12)
  - Tracking log – August 6, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 13)
  - Tracking log – August 9, 1982 (Box-folder 110: 14)
  - Tracking log – August 10, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 1)
  - Tracking log – August 20, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 2)
  - Status of Administration-Sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 1st Session – May 7, 1981 (Box-folder 111: 3)
  - 1981 Public Appearances (Box-folder 111: 4)
  - Office of Cabinet Affairs Issues Schedule – August 13, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 5)
  - Status of Administration-Sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 2nd Session – August 12, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 6)
  - OCA Issue Tracking Reports—Week of November 16, 1981 (Box-folder 111: 7)
  - Status of Administration-Sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 2nd Session – July 22, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 8)
  - Status of Administration-Sponsored Legislation 97th Congress, 2nd Session – April 29, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 9)
  - Office of Cabinet Affairs-Issue Tracking Report III By Staffing and Title – April 26, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 10)
  - The National Economy 1981-Background and Policy Recommendations for 1982 (Box-folder 111: 11)
  - Tracking log – October 1, 1982 (Box-folder 111: 12)
  - Senior Staff Meetings (Box-folder 111: 13)
  - Legislative Highlights (Box-folder 111: 14)
  - Economic/Capital Formation (Box-folder 111: 15)
  - Drug Policy-Hold (Box-folder 111: 16)
  - Cabinet Council on Legal Policy-Drug Supply Reduction 1982 (Box-folder 111: 17)
  - Crime-Drug Initiative (Box-folder 111: 18)
  - Drug Policy (Box-folder 111: 19)
  - EMPB/DPA III (Box-folder 111: 20)
  - Enterprise Zones (Box-folder 112: 1-3)
  - DPA III (Box-folder 112: 4)
  - Women/ERA (Box-folder 112: 5-9)
  - Watch List (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Emergency Mobilization Preparedness Board (EMPB) (Box-folder 113: 2)
  - H.R. 5540 – Defense Industrial Base Revitalization Act (Box-folder 113: 3)
  - Talking Points/Secretary Carlucci (Box-folder 113: 4)
  - Weekly Activities Reports (Box-folder 113: 5)
  - Social Science Working Paper 430 – June 1982 (Box-folder 113: 6)
  - Mid-Term Report on Regulatory Reform (Box-folder 113: 7)
  - Instead of Regulation (Box-folder 113: 8)
  - New York City Loan Guarantees (Box-folder 113: 9)
  - Management Review on the Performance of the U.S. Department of the Treasury (Box-folder 113: 10)
  - OMB (Box-folder 113: 11)
  - Troubled Industries (Box-folder 113: 12)
  - CBMS run of law enforcement activities across agencies (Box-folder 113: 13)
  - Testimony Index – February, 1983 (Box-folder 113: 14)
  - IRS Revenue Yield Methodology (Box-folder 113: 15)
  - Correspondence of Congressman Jim Jones (Box-folder 113: 16)
  - Briefing on Current Budget Outlook – March 17, 1982 (Box-folder 113: 17)
  - Summary of major Congressional alternatives to the FY 83 budget (Box-folder 113: 18)
  - Department of Transportation, 1982 (Box-folder 113: 19)
  - Letters of No Prejudice/DOT (Box-folder 113: 20)
  - Small Business Administration (SBA) (Box-folder 113: 21-22)
  - Transportation Taxes (Box-folder 113: 23)
  - Tin (Box-folder 114: 1)
  - Balanced Budget/tax limitation amendment (Box-folder 114: 2)
  - Growth in Social Contract Spending 1963-1981 – Constant (1983 $) Outlays (Box-folder 114: 3)
  - II. Toward Economic Growth (Box-folder 114: 4)
  - Comparison for 1987 – scrolls/Administration/Planning baseline (Box-folder 114: 5)
  - Inventory of charts (Box-folder 114: 6)
  - OMB pass back/Washington Post article (Box-folder 114: 7)
  - Senior Staff Meeting 1982 (Box-folder 114: 8)
  - Committee on Small Business SBA Farm Disaster Loan Program – September 10, 1981 (Box-folder 114: 9)
  - Rollover of Money Market Certificates and Certificates of Deposit at Savings and Loan Associations (Box-folder 114: 10)
  - FSLIC (Box-folder 114: 11)
  - Tax Bill (Box-folder 114: 12)
  - S. 898 – Telecommunications Competition and Deregulation Act of 1981 (Box-folder 114: 13)
  - The State of the S and L Industry and FHLBB Policy Options (Box-folder 114: 14)
  - Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs – May 7, 1981 (Box-folder 114: 15)
  - Thrifts (Box-folder 114: 16)
  - Current Cash Flow Situation of S and L’s (Box-folder 114: 17)
  - Spring Review – Defense non-DOD (Box-folder 114: 18)
  - Stockpile (Box-folder 114: 19)
  - Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC) (Box-folder 114: 20)
  - War Risk Insurance Bill, H.R. 5930 Talking Points-“Alleghany-Mohawk Provisions” (Box-folder 114: 21)
  - Survey of Income and Program Participation (SIPP) (Box-folder 114: 22)
  - Tax Bill Briefing Material – August 4, 1982 (Box-folder 114: 23)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Official Residence of the Vice President (Box-folder 114: 24)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Office of Policy Development (Box-folder 114: 25)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Office of Personnel Management (Box-folder 114: 26)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Office of Management and Budget (Box-folder 114: 27)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Office of Federal Procurement Policy (Box-folder 114: 28)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Office of Administration (Box-folder 114: 29)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: United States Railway Administration (Box-folder 114: 30)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Securities and Exchange Commission (Box-folder 115: 1)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Pennsylvania Avenue Development Corporation (Box-folder 115: 2)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Panama Canal Commission (Box-folder 115: 3)
  - Speeches Given (Box-folder 115: 4)
  - Comments of David A. Stockman Before the House Republican Conference – September 16, 1981 (Box-folder 115: 5)
  - Fall Budget Program – September 24, 1981 (Box-folder 115: 6)
  - Fact Sheet on FY 1982 Budget Amendments (Box-folder 115: 7)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) (Box-folder 115: 8)
  - Agency Operations in the Absence of Appropriations (Box-folder 115: 9)
  - Analysis of Economic Recovery Tax Act (ERTA) Effects on Private Sector Expenditures (Box-folder 115: 10)
  - Steel (Box-folder 115: 11)
  - Small Agencies – 82 Appeals/83-84 Budget (Box-folder 115: 12-13)
  - Personnel (Box-folder 115: 14)
  - Housing Stack (Box-folder 115: 15)
  - Summary Fact Sheet on the Reagan Administration Housing Policy (Box-folder 115: 16)
  - Statement of Lawrence A. Kudlow (Box-folder 115: 17)
  - Treasury – 83-84 Budget (Box-folder 115: 18)
  - Amendments to S. 533 Reflecting Discussion with OMB Staff (Box-folder 115: 19)
  - Housing Industry in Singapore (Box-folder 115: 20)
  - B. Guard Notes (Box-folder 115: 21)
  - Gas Tax/Transportation (Box-folder 115: 22)
  - Small Agencies (Box-folder 115: 23)
  - Neighborhood Reinvestment Corporation (NCR) (Box-folder 115: 24)
  - Approval Sheet- Agency: Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (Box-folder 115: 25)
  - Copy of the letter sent by Max Friedersdorf and Dave Stockman/Set of tables of the reconciliation assumptions (Box-folder 115: 26)
  - Supplementals (Box-folder 115: 27)
  - Change Highlights on Preliminary Senate Subcommittee Action – Table of Contents (Box-folder 116: 1)
  - First Budget Resolution/Legislative Affairs (Box-folder 116: 2)
  - Upcoming Hearings and Markups – May 1, 1981 (Box-folder 116: 3)
  - Status of Remaining Administration Legislation (Box-folder 116: 4)
  - Senate (Selected) Week of May 4-8 (Box-folder 116: 5)
  - Private Sector Initiative (Box-folder 116: 6)
  - Revenue Estimates for sale of real property (Box-folder 116: 7)
  - The Stockman Manifesto and Housing Policy – Robert M. Buckley (Box-folder 116: 8)
  - Public Buildings Act (Box-folder 116: 9)
  - Senate rail authorization bill (Box-folder 116: 10)
  - Reconciliation (Box-folder 116: 11)
  - Final-Final Version of Preliminary Summary of Reconciliation Bill (Box-folder 116: 12)
  - Final Draft of Summary of Omnibus Budget Reconciliation Act of 1981, H.R. 3982 (Box-folder 116: 13)
  - Experimenting With Housing Allowances Executive Summary (Box-folder 116: 14)
  - Enrolled Bill H.R. 6267 – Garn-St. Germain Depository Institutions Act of 1982 (Box-folder 116: 15)
  - Note to David Stockman from Pete Modlin – October 16, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 16)
  - Possible Committee Changes in the New Congress (Box-folder 116: 17)
  - House Races (Interim) (Box-folder 116: 18)
  - FDIC/FEC/Treasury/OPM/CPB/DC note cards (Box-folder 116: 19)
  - Federal Emergency Management Agency Overview (Box-folder 116: 20)
  - S. 2411 – Justice Assistance Act of 1982 (Box-folder 116: 21)
  - Major Themes 1984 (Box-folder 116: 22)
  - Friday Night Money Supply/Credit Market Report (Box-folder 116: 23)
  - Network News Summary for Tuesday Evening, November 16, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 24)
  - CCNRE Meeting (1/28) – Natural Gas Decontrol (Box-folder 116: 25)
  - Letter to Senator Heinz in response to his November 11 letter – 1982 (Box-folder 116: 26)
  - Current legislative status of various DOT bills (Box-folder 116: 27)
  - Congressional action on the SLUC fund (Box-folder 116: 28)
  - Tracking log – October 22/29, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 29)
  - Producer Prices and Industrial Production in September (Box-folder 116: 30)
  - CCEA Minutes (Box-folder 116: 31)